{"qid": "easy-coffee-0000", "question": "What was the opening price of coffee on 2001-12-06?", "answer": "42.75"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0001", "question": "What was the opening price of coffee on 2014-11-24?", "answer": "190.5"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0002", "question": "What was the opening price of coffee on 2013-07-23?", "answer": "125.4"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0003", "question": "What was the opening price of coffee on 2000-04-11?", "answer": "96.0"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0004", "question": "What was the opening price of coffee on 2007-04-09?", "answer": "110.85"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0005", "question": "What was the opening price of coffee on 2009-06-11?", "answer": "130.8"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0006", "question": "What was the opening price of coffee on 2005-07-18?", "answer": "102.5"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0007", "question": "What was the opening price of coffee on 2018-06-11?", "answer": "117.25"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0008", "question": "What was the opening price of coffee on 2021-04-09?", "answer": "127.9"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0009", "question": "What was the opening price of coffee on 2017-05-09?", "answer": "132.8"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0010", "question": "What was the opening price of coffee on 2013-12-26?", "answer": "114.95"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0011", "question": "What was the opening price of coffee on 2011-05-18?", "answer": "268.0"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0012", "question": "What was the opening price of coffee on 2018-03-06?", "answer": "120.1"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0013", "question": "What was the lowest price of coffee on 2016-12-23?", "answer": "135.95"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0014", "question": "What was the lowest price of coffee on 2020-04-20?", "answer": "113.05"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0015", "question": "What was the lowest price of coffee on 2000-09-13?", "answer": "79.0"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0016", "question": "What was the lowest price of coffee on 2016-08-31?", "answer": "144.7"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0017", "question": "What was the lowest price of coffee on 2008-12-19?", "answer": "110.25"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0018", "question": "What was the lowest price of coffee on 2010-04-12?", "answer": "133.05"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0019", "question": "What was the lowest price of coffee on 2005-01-27?", "answer": "103.05"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0020", "question": "What was the lowest price of coffee on 2004-09-27?", "answer": "83.3"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0021", "question": "What was the lowest price of coffee on 2000-05-25?", "answer": "98.5"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0022", "question": "What was the lowest price of coffee on 2011-03-07?", "answer": "275.0"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0023", "question": "What was the lowest price of coffee on 2005-09-26?", "answer": "88.15"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0024", "question": "What was the lowest price of coffee on 2004-06-09?", "answer": "80.65"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0025", "question": "What was the lowest price of coffee on 2018-05-03?", "answer": "122.45"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0026", "question": "What was the highest price of coffee on 2002-10-08?", "answer": "58.6"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0027", "question": "What was the highest price of coffee on 2012-11-12?", "answer": "154.4"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0028", "question": "What was the highest price of coffee on 2000-03-06?", "answer": "106.5"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0029", "question": "What was the highest price of coffee on 2002-11-18?", "answer": "68.0"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0030", "question": "What was the highest price of coffee on 2013-09-10?", "answer": "114.6"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0031", "question": "What was the highest price of coffee on 2022-06-24?", "answer": "234.45"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0032", "question": "What was the highest price of coffee on 2021-10-22?", "answer": "206.4"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0033", "question": "What was the highest price of coffee on 2011-12-16?", "answer": "214.25"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0034", "question": "What was the highest price of coffee on 2015-11-24?", "answer": "123.0"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0035", "question": "What was the highest price of coffee on 2021-02-10?", "answer": "123.55"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0036", "question": "What was the highest price of coffee on 2016-08-10?", "answer": "141.75"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0037", "question": "What was the highest price of coffee on 2001-04-23?", "answer": "62.0"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0038", "question": "What was the highest price of coffee on 2002-11-12?", "answer": "65.0"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0039", "question": "What was the closing price of coffee on 2017-09-12?", "answer": "133.8"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0040", "question": "What was the closing price of coffee on 2010-11-05?", "answer": "205.15"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0041", "question": "What was the closing price of coffee on 2008-01-30?", "answer": "136.55"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0042", "question": "What was the closing price of coffee on 2009-09-09?", "answer": "123.7"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0043", "question": "What was the closing price of coffee on 2002-09-30?", "answer": "54.5"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0044", "question": "What was the closing price of coffee on 2001-01-22?", "answer": "71.25"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0045", "question": "What was the closing price of coffee on 2005-08-19?", "answer": "96.1"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0046", "question": "What was the closing price of coffee on 2002-07-03?", "answer": "48.15"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0047", "question": "What was the closing price of coffee on 2015-04-29?", "answer": "138.35"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0048", "question": "What was the closing price of coffee on 2018-06-21?", "answer": "112.6"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0049", "question": "What was the closing price of coffee on 2008-08-06?", "answer": "137.9"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0050", "question": "What was the closing price of coffee on 2001-03-15?", "answer": "59.1"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0051", "question": "What was the closing price of coffee on 2013-07-02?", "answer": "124.1"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0052", "question": "What was the volume of coffee on 2003-09-15?", "answer": "75"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0053", "question": "What was the volume of coffee on 2020-06-24?", "answer": "34"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0054", "question": "What was the volume of coffee on 2012-04-30?", "answer": "28"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0055", "question": "What was the volume of coffee on 2002-05-20?", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0056", "question": "What was the volume of coffee on 2009-03-09?", "answer": "6"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0057", "question": "What was the volume of coffee on 2004-12-16?", "answer": "78"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0058", "question": "What was the volume of coffee on 2013-09-11?", "answer": "11"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0059", "question": "What was the volume of coffee on 2013-06-21?", "answer": "119"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0060", "question": "What was the volume of coffee on 2013-04-08?", "answer": "33418"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0061", "question": "What was the volume of coffee on 2017-01-30?", "answer": "14830"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0062", "question": "What was the volume of coffee on 2021-04-12?", "answer": "23948"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0063", "question": "What was the volume of coffee on 2015-05-28?", "answer": "11730"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0064", "question": "What was the percentage change in coffee price on 2017-05-18, based on the difference between the opening and closing prices?", "answer": "-1.39%"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0065", "question": "What was the percentage change in coffee price on 2021-03-01, based on the difference between the opening and closing prices?", "answer": "-2.38%"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0066", "question": "What was the percentage change in coffee price on 2015-04-27, based on the difference between the opening and closing prices?", "answer": "-2.79%"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0067", "question": "What was the percentage change in coffee price on 2015-05-15, based on the difference between the opening and closing prices?", "answer": "-0.54%"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0068", "question": "What was the percentage change in coffee price on 2014-12-21, based on the difference between the opening and closing prices?", "answer": "0.0%"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0069", "question": "What was the percentage change in coffee price on 2006-11-06, based on the difference between the opening and closing prices?", "answer": "-0.26%"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0070", "question": "What was the percentage change in coffee price on 2016-04-01, based on the difference between the opening and closing prices?", "answer": "-0.08%"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0071", "question": "What was the percentage change in coffee price on 2019-12-16, based on the difference between the opening and closing prices?", "answer": "-0.04%"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0072", "question": "What was the percentage change in coffee price on 2007-04-10, based on the difference between the opening and closing prices?", "answer": "-0.36%"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0073", "question": "What was the percentage change in coffee price on 2002-08-21, based on the difference between the opening and closing prices?", "answer": "-0.11%"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0074", "question": "What was the percentage change in coffee price on 2003-10-14, based on the difference between the opening and closing prices?", "answer": "1.82%"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0075", "question": "What was the percentage change in coffee price on 2004-10-08, based on the difference between the opening and closing prices?", "answer": "-1.15%"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0076", "question": "Was 2016-04-20 a bearish or bullish day for coffee price?", "answer": "bullish"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0077", "question": "Was 2012-08-23 a bearish or bullish day for coffee price?", "answer": "bullish"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0078", "question": "Was 2013-07-26 a bearish or bullish day for coffee price?", "answer": "bearish"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0079", "question": "Was 2004-08-23 a bearish or bullish day for coffee price?", "answer": "bullish"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0080", "question": "Was 2009-04-29 a bearish or bullish day for coffee price?", "answer": "bullish"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0081", "question": "Was 2011-07-12 a bearish or bullish day for coffee price?", "answer": "bearish"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0082", "question": "Was 2017-06-12 a bearish or bullish day for coffee price?", "answer": "bullish"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0083", "question": "Was 2001-09-17 a bearish or bullish day for coffee price?", "answer": "bearish"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0084", "question": "Was 2020-04-16 a bearish or bullish day for coffee price?", "answer": "bearish"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0085", "question": "Was 2007-11-14 a bearish or bullish day for coffee price?", "answer": "bullish"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0086", "question": "Was 2007-04-02 a bearish or bullish day for coffee price?", "answer": "bearish"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0087", "question": "Was 2021-05-19 a bearish or bullish day for coffee price?", "answer": "bearish"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0088", "question": "What was the range of coffee price on 2018-07-06, based on the difference between the high and low prices??", "answer": "2.05"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0089", "question": "What was the range of coffee price on 2002-04-09, based on the difference between the high and low prices??", "answer": "2.5"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0090", "question": "What was the range of coffee price on 2017-09-28, based on the difference between the high and low prices??", "answer": "2.2"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0091", "question": "What was the range of coffee price on 2020-07-07, based on the difference between the high and low prices??", "answer": "3.35"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0092", "question": "What was the range of coffee price on 2012-04-18, based on the difference between the high and low prices??", "answer": "2.1"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0093", "question": "What was the range of coffee price on 2018-05-07, based on the difference between the high and low prices??", "answer": "1.1"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0094", "question": "What was the range of coffee price on 2021-06-18, based on the difference between the high and low prices??", "answer": "3.95"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0095", "question": "What was the range of coffee price on 2007-05-04, based on the difference between the high and low prices??", "answer": "0.0"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0096", "question": "What was the range of coffee price on 2004-08-06, based on the difference between the high and low prices??", "answer": "1.95"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0097", "question": "What was the range of coffee price on 2007-10-22, based on the difference between the high and low prices??", "answer": "3.85"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0098", "question": "What was the range of coffee price on 2006-05-11, based on the difference between the high and low prices??", "answer": "3.5"}
{"qid": "easy-coffee-0099", "question": "What was the range of coffee price on 2020-09-22, based on the difference between the high and low prices??", "answer": "4.45"}
